<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/ukdpnhblog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/ukdpnhblog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-03-03T17:33:01+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/ukdpnhblog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">PayN’Halt Blog</title><subtitle>The Idea Of PayNHalt Was Conceived In Year 2018 By The Bunch Of IT Professionals.  They Worked On The Idea Tirelessly And Finally The Idea Was Transformed In Reality In 2019.  PayNHalt App Is Designed To Meet Your Day To Day Parking Problems.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Parking problems in metropolitan cities in india!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/ukdpnhblog/parkingsolutions/2019/03/03/welcome-to-paynhalt.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Parking problems in metropolitan cities in india!" /><published>2019-03-03T15:49:45+05:30</published><updated>2019-03-03T15:49:45+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/ukdpnhblog/parkingsolutions/2019/03/03/welcome-to-paynhalt</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/ukdpnhblog/parkingsolutions/2019/03/03/welcome-to-paynhalt.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/c0dc94f2-d3e7-483d-b550-c21ef671f4ba.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My helpful screenshot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indian automobile market has long growth story. The growth had picked up after the 1991 economic liberalisation.
Rapid growth of vehicle let to a parking problems, special in metropolitan cities like Mumbai.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyhow the fact is buying a new car is no longer a status symbol at least in the metropolitan cities and is more of a necessity. But as in there has been a wide gap in the growth of infrastructure and the growth of our Indian automobile industry there is already a big huge parking problem that the country faces today&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We at PayNHalt has come up with Smart Parking solution that combines technology and human innovation in an effort to achieve faster, easier and denser parking of vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now with PayNHalt app in place your parking space is at your fingertips .
Install PayNHalt today to experience the difference in your daily parking habits.
Be the part of Change!!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>